wowparadise.biz 2009-10-03

# 

## WOW Paradise Privacy Policy

WOW Paradise have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

### IP Address

WOW Paradise use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your activity on our website.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. By setting a cookie on our site, the user should not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.

### Log Files

WOW Paradise collects information on our site visitors collectively, including which sections of the site are most frequently visited, how often and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-personal information. WOW Paradise utilizes this information to improve and enhance our services by monitoring the areas on the site which are most popular to you. The data collected is not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Updating Membership Information

Users' membership information (such as postal address, phone numbers, email address, etc) can be updated via the details located on the member's website. Alternatively the member can place a request for changing this information with WOW Paradise via the support ticket system.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

### Choice/Opt-Out

In any correspondence with our customers, they are given the choice to be removed from our database simply by clicking the remove/unsubscribe link at the bottom of all out going messages.

### Notification Of Changes

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this web page so our users are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please send an email to team(at)wowparadise(dot)biz
